Guide to the Stanford University, Michelle R. Clayman Institute for Gender Research, Records SC0705
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Audiorecordings, Accession ARCH-2004-126
  - Fall Seminar: Laura Carstensen, 1999 Nov 9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 24)
  - Associate's Day Seminar: Sheila Lewis, 1999-05-27; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 24)
  - Associate's Day Seminar: Estelle Freedman, 2000 Feb 29; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 24)
  - Associates' Day Seminar: Packer & Spiegel, 2000 Feb; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 24)
  - Lyman Lecture: Laura Carstensen, 2000 Mar 1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 24)
  - Breakfast Seminar: Marjorie Hansen Shaevitz, 2000-03-9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 24)
  - Lyman Lecture: Fredia Brooks, 2000-04-13; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 24)
  - Lyman Lecture: Dennis Carter--"Osteoporosis and Arthritis: physical activity and a healthy skeleton", 2000-04-26; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 24)
  - Associate's Seminar: Ruth O'Hara--"Estrogen, Cognitive Function, and Risk of Alzheimer's", 2000-05-3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 24)
  - Breakfast Seminar: Catherine S. Muther--"Venture Philanthropy in the New Economy: Women's Technology Cluster", 2000-05-9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 24)
  - Lyman Lecture: Robert Friedland--"Is Demography Destiny?", 2000-05-24; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 24)
  - Lyman Lecture: Gwen Yeo--"The Ethnogeriatric Imperative and its Implications", 2000-10-4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 24)
  - Associate's Fall Seminar: Linda Darling-Hammond--"Teaching and Learning in the 21st Century", 2000-10-17; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 24)
  - Rhode, Deborah L., lecture: Betty Friedan and panelists Laura Carstensen, Carroll Estes, Deborah Rhode, Myra Strober, 2000 Nov 8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 24)
  - Breakfast Seminar: Kim Walesh--"Preliminary Research Results on Women's Leadership in the New Economy", 2000-11-14; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 24)
  - Lyman Lecture: Elizabeth Roden--"Aging and the Media", 2000-12-6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 24)
  - Lyman Lecture: Rabbi Patricia Karlin-Neumann--"Firstfruits: Contemporary Women's Contributions to Religious Traditions", 2001-02-21; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 24)
  - Breakfast Seminar: Aida Sabo--"Creativity and Innovation through Diversity", 2001 Feb 28; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 24)
  - Lyman Lecture: Yvonne Yarbro-Bejarano--"Writing the Lesbian Mother: 'Waiting in the Wings' by Cherrie Moraga", 2001-05-16; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 24)
  - Lyman Lecture: Joel Beinin--"Palestinian Women: Between National Struggle and Female Emancipation", 2001-04-25; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 24)
  - Associate's Seminar: Marcia Stefanick--"Postmenopausal Hormone Replacement Therapy: New Controversies", 2001-05-2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 24)
  - Lyman Lecture: John Jost--"The Psychology of Deservingness: Overcoming Ambivalence and Depressed Entitlement in Women", 2001-05-10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 24)
  - Corporate Breakfast Seminar: Judy Estrin--"The Internet and Women: The Great Equalizer?", 2001 Sept. 13; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 24)
  - Lyman Lecture: Diann McCants, 2001 Oct 24; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 24)
  - Lyman Lecture: Purnima Mankekar, 2001 Nov 14; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 24)
  - Lyman Lecture: Yoshiko Matsumoto, 2001 Dec 5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 24)
  - Associate's Day: Pamela Karlan, 2002-01-30; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - Lyman Lecture: Myra Strober, 2002 Apr 3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - Spring Open House: Ashraf Zahedi: "Women's Rights in the Middle East: Myth vs. Reality", 2002-05-22; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - Spring Open House: Peggy Drexler--"Can Mothers Make Men? The Impact of Single Mother and Gay Mother Relationships on Their Sons", 2002-05-22; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - Spring Open House: Saskia Traill--"Vulnerability Factors in Adolescent Girls at Risk for Depression", 2002-05-22; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - "Eccles Talk"--Jacquelynne Eccles, 2002-10-14; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - Lyman Lecture: Jeanne Tsai--“IMMIGRANT FAMILIES: THE EFFECTS OF ACCULTURATION ON PARENT-CHILD RELATIONSHIPS, 2002 Dec 4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - Associate's Board Seminar: Patti Chang, 2002 Dec 10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - Lyman Lecture: Amado Padilla, 2003-10-9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - Lyman Lecture: Michele Y. Pridmore-Brown--The Bio-Politics of Delayed [i.e., Late] Motherhood, 2002 Apr 24; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - Lyman Lecture: Pamela Matson--"Science at the Margins", 2003-10-8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - Lyman Lecture: Sheri Sheppard, 2003 Nov 5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - Lyman Lecture: Carol Muller, 2003 Dec 3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - Lyman Lecture: Arthur Bienenstock, 2003-02-26; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - Lyman Lecture: Barbara Voss, 2004-01-20; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - Lyman Lecture: Deborah Gordon--“ANTS AT WORK: THE ORGANIZATION OF SOCIAL INSECT COLONIES”, 2004-02-11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - Lyman Lecture: Theresa Isaacs, 2001-11-13; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - Lyman Series Winter Conference: Theoretical Perspectives on Sexual Difference: Feminist Ethical and Political Theory. Carol MacKay on Anne Thackeray Ritchie; Marnie Jones on V. Woolf's biography of Roger Fry. Lucio Ruotolo, commentator, 2004 Feb 19; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - Lyman Series Winter Conference: Q&A with MacKay and Jones, 2004 Feb 19; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - CROW Conference: German Women's Autobiographies, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - CROW Conference: German Women's Autobiographies Tape 2, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - Women Office Workers Organize; TV and Children. Produced by The Rest of the News, Ithaca NY, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - Quotations about Women. Produced by The Rest of the News, Ithaca NY, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - Sexism in Children's Books; Toys. Produced by The Rest of the News, Ithaca NY, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - Women and Health Care lecture series: Helen Blau--"Amniocentesis, Prenatal Care and Genetic Counseling", 1980 Jan 16; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Lyman Lecture Series: Marcia Falk--"Spiritual Journey of a Jewish Feminist", 1986 Jan 29; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
  - Nigel Nicholson--"Virginia Woolf: Letter and Diaries", 1977 Nov 30; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - CROW Group: Carol Idehlin, Eleanor Maccoby, 1978 Jan 9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - lecture: Howard & Nancy Tamler--"Becoming Parents, Remaining Partners"; Ann & Robert DeBusk--"Coping with the Stress of Sickness" [Rat Race Seminar on Partners], 1979 Jan 20; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Two lectures on Western Culture: Barbara Meyerhof--"Women's Culture" [#2], 1979 Nov 9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - CROW lecture series: Marcia Falk--"Spiritual Journey of a Jewish Feminist", 1986 Jan 29; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
  - Associates' Day 1987, 1987 Feb 5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Associates' Day 1987, 1987 Feb 5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Associates Program: Salon Seminar, 1987-03-18; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Associates Salon Seminar, 1987-04-21; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Faculty Fellowship in Women's Health, 1993-05-25; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 18)
  - Health Forum, 1994-01-3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 20)
  - Oral history interview: Margaret. Sources of Strength. Women's Educdational Equity Act Program, Dept. of HEW, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - Oral history interview: Guadelupe. Sources of Strength. Women's Educdational Equity Act Program, Dept. of HEW, 1991; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - Motherhood: Personal & Professional Considerations. Intro; Options for Women (Diana Paul, Lucy Scott, Pamela Eakins); New Parents (Lanie Powers Patricia Brandt, Joanne Martin, Wyn Kelley) Part 1, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - Motherhood: Personal & Professional Considerations. New parents (Wyn Kelley, David Spiegel); Parenting in Academe (Carol Muller, Patricia Joplin, Barrie Thorne) part 2, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - Gender, Race and Class: Bonnie Thornton Dill--"Survival as a Form of Resistance", 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - Naomi Katz--Anthro. Prof. SF State, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - Gender, Race and Class: Panel--Fong, Chacon & Medicine CROW noon lecture -05-19 [no year], 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - Kay Boyle tape 1, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - Kay Boyle tape 2, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - Kay Boyle tape 3, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - Associates' Day: Ronald Rebholz--"Shakespeare's Women", 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - Associates' Day 1991: Iris Litt--"Women and Health"; Carolyn Lougee - "Eleanor of Aquitaine & Joan of Arc" (& Madame Bovary), 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 25)
  - Emma Goldman: The courage to struggle, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 26)
  - O'Leary [?], 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 26)
  - Clinical implications of female [?] therapy, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 26)
  - Corporate Seminar: [seminar talk], 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 26)
- Records, Accession ARCH-2004-152
  - AFFILIATED SCHOLARS
    - Adams, Judith Porter (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Andrews, Cecile (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Andrews, Naomi (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Aruga, Natsuke (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Belyea, Marlou (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Betts, Diane C. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Bihary, Sheila (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Birnbaum, Lucia Chiavola (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Birnbaum, Paula (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Blodgett, Harriet (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Bodine, Ann (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Boufis, Christina (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Boxer, Marilyn (2 folders) (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Breslin, Glenna (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Brown, Stephanie (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Burce, Amy (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Burke, Carolyn C. (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Cancino, Herlinda (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Catacalos, Rosemary (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Cruikshank, Margaret (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Dillon, Millicent (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Drexler, Peggy (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Eakins, Pamela (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Elworth, Julie (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Edwards, Julie Olsen (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Falk, Marcia (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Faludi, Susan (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Farmer, Elspeth (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Gillespie, Joanna (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Gleason, Maud (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Golan, Daphna (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Golde, Peggy (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Gottheil, Ellen (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Handwerker, Lisa (2 folders) (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Herman, Sondra (2 folders) (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Holloman, Gina (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Horn, Margo (2 folders) (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Iandoli, CeCe (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Johnson, Karen (3 folders) (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Jones, Judith Z. (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Junkerman, Christine (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Kanner, Barbara (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Karpilow, Kathleen (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Kassabian, Anahid (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Katchadourian, Stina (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Kawashima, Yoko (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Keeshen, Kay (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Klaus, Patricia Otto (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Klaw, Elena (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Krieger, Susan (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Langendorf, Adele (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Lawson, Annette (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Lewin, Ellen (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Linden, Ruth (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - MacKinnon, Catharine A. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Magnus, Shulamit (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Malveaux, Julianne (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Matthews, Glenna (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - McCauley, Nancy (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - McTigue, Geraldine (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Meier, Gretl S. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Menke, Anne (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Milone, Pauline (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Munkhoff, Richelle (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Murray, Aife (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Myers, Sylvia (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Norwood, Lisa West (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Novak, Jane (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Olsen, Victoria (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - O'Reilly-Brewster, Wenda (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Packer, Barbara (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Parreno, Margarita (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Rao, Nancy (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Ring, Jennifer (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Robinson, Lillian (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Roscoe, Will (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Rosenblum, Barbara (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Rosenhan, Mollie (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Rosenthal, Jane (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Sagan, Ginetta (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Salner, Marcia (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Shahzade, Susan A. (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Sibbet, Susan (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Skold, Karen Beck (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Sohoni, Neera (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Stahr, Celia (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Stange, Margrit (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Stanley, Autumn (2 folders) (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Steinberg, Jill (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Stern, Bat-Sheva (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Stich, Sidra (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Stockard, Janice (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Walker, Cherryl (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Walker-Moffat, Wendy (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Wanat, Stan [has financial info – remove] (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Way, Brenda (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Weinstein, Harvey (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Wolf, Margery [this file not in box] (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Wuerth, Andrea (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Zheng, Wang (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - VISITING SCHOLARS
    - Achuthan, Nisha (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Allen, Ann T. (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Allen, Jeffner (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Anderson, Linda (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Arnold, Stephanie (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Auerhahn, Nanette (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Baker, Therese (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Bernardez, Teresa (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Bielby, Denise (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Biersack, Aletta (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Blevins, Juliette (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Blom, Ida (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Blumberg, Rhoda L. (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Botcheva, Luba (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Boyd, Nan (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Bronstein, Phyllis (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Brown, Judith (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Brunazzi, Elizabeth (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Carbone, June (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Carew, Jean V. (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Carlen, Pat (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Chadwick, Whitney (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Chancer, Lynn (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Chatterjee, Martha (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Choong, Poh Lian (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Chou, Bih E. (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Conefrey, Theresa (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Coker, Donna (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Corr, Helen (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Cova, Anne (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Curtis, Sarah (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Ducker, Dalia (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Dalziel, Raewyn (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Daniels, Arlene K. (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Davison, Jean (2) (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Diebolt, Evelyne (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Dogramaci, Emel (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Douglass, Lisa (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Duquin, Mary E. (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Epstein, Cynthia Fuchs (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Espin, Oliva (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Ezekiel, Judith (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Fazeli, Rafat (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Felstiner, Mary Lowenthal (2) (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Ferber, Marianne A. (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Ffolliott, Sheila (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Fishkin, Shelley (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Ford, Joan (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Frankenhaeuser, Marianne (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Freitag, Kornelia (2) (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Freiwald, Bina (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Frye, Susan (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Funk, Ursula (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Gardiner, Judith K. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Gillett, Paula (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Goldberg, Marilyn (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Goldschmidt-Clermont, Luisella (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Goodman, Bryna (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Goodstein, Lynne [this file not in box] (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Gorham, Deborah (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Hansen, Susan (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Hansot, Elizabeth (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Harsch, Donna (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Hartnett, Oonagh (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Hawkes, Ellen (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Henderson, Lynne (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Holahan, Carol (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Hoogland, Renee (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - How, Janice (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Hull, Gloria (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Ilumoka, Toun (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Iseman, Kay (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Jecker, Nancy (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Jones, Kathleen (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Jones, Nancy (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Jung, Jin Hwa (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Katzenstein, Mary F. (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Keohane, Nannerl (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Keys, David E. (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Killam, Rosemary (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Ku, Yenlin (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Kuhn, Anna K. (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Kwon, Yung-Hee (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Lara, Maria Pia (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Lashof, Carol (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Lauver, Diane (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Lee, Aldora (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Lee, Judith (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Lerner, Jacqueline (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Lester, Toni (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Lidoff, Joan I. (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Lomperis, Linda (3) (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Lorence-Kot, Bogna (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Lott, Bernice (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Luria, Zella (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Ma, Yanling (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - MacCorquodale, Patricia (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Mahony, Rhona (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Manlapaz, Edna Zapanta (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Maurer, Kathryn (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Martin, Wendy (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - McCoy, Norma L. (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - McCurry, Stephanie (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - McDonagh, Josephine (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Meyerson, Debra (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Mohanram, Radhika (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Morita, Akiharu (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Murphy, Julien (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Neyer, Gerda (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - O'Brien, Leslie (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Owens, Robyn (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Parker, Lyn (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Pearce, Diana (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Pedersen, Tove Beate (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Peel, Ellen (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Pettegrew, John (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Phillips, Kathy (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Pineau, Claude (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Ping, Li (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Pittin, Renee (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Plasai, Valaikanya (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Porter, Paige (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Prentice, Alison (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Rabine, Leslie W. (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Reame, Nancy (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Reeves, Nancy (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Reich, Nancy (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Reskin, Barbara (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Richardson, Sarah (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Riger, Stephanie (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Romito, Patrizia (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Rorty, Mary (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Ross, Janice (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Rothblum, Esther (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Sadoff, Dianne (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Safir, Marilyn (2) (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Sanger, Carol (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Sansbury, Gail (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Schaffer, Diane M. (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Schuster, Marilyn (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Seshachari, Neila (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Shiri, Sonia (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Shoemaker, Robert (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Shostak, Marjorie (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Siim, Birte (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Silvers, Anita (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Soh, Sarah C. (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Staudt, Nancy (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Strasser, Sabine (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Sugarman, Jane (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Suh, Ji Moon (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Sundquist, Asebrit (2) (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Swain, Carol (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Takeda, Takako (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Thebaud, Francoise (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Thomas, Joyce C. (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Thorne, Barrie (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Ullian, Dorothy (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Urruella, Maria (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Vajanasoontorn, Penkae (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Reception / dinner visiting scholar Thailand (Box 6, Folder 3.1)
    - Van Dyne, Susan (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Voda, Ann M. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Walker, Brenda (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Wang, Qihui (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Ward, Cynthia (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Weiler, Kathleen (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Weimer, Joan (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Weitzman, Lenore (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Whitney, Karen (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Williams, Patricia (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Wilson, Lindsay (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Wyche, Karen (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Yishai, Yael (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Yoshizumi, Kyoko (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - SCHOLAR APPLICANTS NOT ACCEPTED
    - Anthony, Dena (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Bandhauer-Schoeffmann, Irene (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Burgard, Deborah (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Conell, Carol (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Divoky, Diane (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Fraser, Mary (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Gelber, Marilyn (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Isaacson, Lanae (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Jing, Huaibin (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Lee, Cynthia (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Luria, Sarah (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - McKibben, Carol (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Nason, Deborah (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Petit-Skinner, Solange (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Reich, Pauline (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Robinson-Walker, Catherine (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Zhang, Xiaohe (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Zheng, Song (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - CORRESPONDENCE
    - Barbara Gelpi Correspondence (3 folders) (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Laura Carstensen Correspondence (4 folders) (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Ineko Tsuchida Correspondence (3 folders) (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Dorothy Steele Correspondence (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Reorganization of Scholars Program 2004 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Iris Litt Correspondence (6 folders) (Box 7)
  - AFRICAN VISITING SCHOLARS
    - Affiliated Scholar Applicants (current year) (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Visiting Scholar Applicants (current year) (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Aina, Olabisi (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Baliddawa, Joyce (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Barclay, Claire (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Bendl, Regine (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Bradford, Helen (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Ebrahim, Haseenah (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Emetarom, Grace (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Fester, Gertrude (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Fujiwara, Barbara (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Kasente, Deborah (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Kivamba, Joyce (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Lewis, Desiree (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Mannathoko, Changu (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Mebrahtu, Saba (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Michael, Cheryl-Ann (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Mirie, Waithira (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Mutoro, Basilida (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Mwalwenje, Dora Victoria (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Ogundipe, Leslie Molara (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Odero, Damaris (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Osojo, Theresa Taiwo (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Raul, Kassea (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Sackey, Brigid (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Sikwibele, Anne (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Sule, Saadatu (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Troy, Maria Holmgren (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Udegbe, I. Bola (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Wasunna, Angela (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Wilson, Vanessa (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Weinbaum, Elfie (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - IRWG History/Newsletters
    - History (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Newsletter binder Fall 1990-Spring 1994 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Newsletter binder Fall 1990-Spring 1994 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - CROW Newsletter Winter 1975-Summer 1981 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Newsletter binder Fall 1981-Spring 1990 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Newsletter binder Fall 1981-Spring 1990 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - IRWG Newsletters Winter 2004 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - IRWG Newsletters Spring/Summer 2003 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - IRWG Newsletters Winter 2003 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - IRWG Newsletters Fall 2002 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - IRWG Newsletters Spring/Summer 2002 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - IRWG Newsletters Winter 2002 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - IRWG Newsletters Fall 2001 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - IRWG Newsletters Spring/Summer 2001 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - IRWG Newsletters Winter 2001 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - IRWG Newsletters Fall 2000 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - IRWG Newsletters Summer 2000 (Box 8, Folder 11)